<resources>
    <!-- All information from the Eugene, Cascades and Coast website. https://www.eugenecascadescoast.org/eugene/ -->
    <string name="app_name">Tour Eugene</string>
    <string name="fragment_eat">Eat</string>
    <string name="fragment_stay">Stay</string>
    <string name="fragment_play">Play</string>
    <string name="fragment_arts">Arts</string>
    <string name="valley_river_name">Valley River Inn</string>
    <string name="valley_river_address">1000 Valley River Way\nEugene OR 97401</string>
    <string name="valley_river_phone">541.743.1000</string>
    <string name="valley_river_website">https://www.valleyriverinn.com/</string>
    <string name="valley_river_details">Staged on the Willamette River, the Valley River Inn
        welcomes guests home. From local cuisine at SweetWaters, art from the city and a staff that
        embraces the spirit of local hospitality; they embody what it truly means to be Eugene.
        Embracing the region’s history, they provide genuinely warm Pacific Northwest hospitality
        with a stunning riverfront location. The 15,000 sq ft of meeting space includes three
        ballrooms. Along with the unmatched scenic views; professional staff and a comfortable
        and relaxing atmosphere make your family event, corporate meeting, or special occasion
        one to remember.</string>
    <string name="inn_at_5th_name">Inn at the 5th</string>
    <string name="inn_at_5th_address">205 E 6th Ave\nEugene OR 97401</string>
    <string name="inn_at_5th_phone">541.743.4099</string>
    <string name="inn_at_5th_website">https://www.innat5th.com/</string>
    <string name="inn_at_5th_details">Located in the 5th Street Public Market in downtown Eugene,
        the Inn at the 5th is a four diamond boutique hotel featuring a variety of guestrooms and
        suites with fireplaces, window-seats, balconies and unique decor. Other amenities include
        complimentary cruiser bikes, room service, butler pantries, fitness room, complimentary
        Wi-Fi, business centers and complimentary glass of wine on arrival, as well as complimentary
        snacks and beverages. Gourmet dining and room-service provided by Marché and salon and spa
        services are provided by Gervais Salon and Spa. Meeting space available.
</string>
    <string name="campbell_house_name">Campbell House</string>
    <string name="campbell_house_address">252 Pearl St\nEugene OR 97401</string>
    <string name="campbell_house_phone">541.343.1119</string>
    <string name="campbell_house_website">https://www.campbellhouse.com/</string>
    <string name="campbell_house_details">A luxurious Eugene bed and breakfast in a garden setting
        overlooking downtown Eugene and known for its charming accommodations and comforts. Built in
        1892 and restored in the tradition of a fine European hotel. Elegant guest rooms feature
        luxury amenities. Catering to business and leisure travel and available for weddings,
        receptions and business meetings. Inquire about special events from tea to dinners.
        Nestled against Skinners Butte and in close proximity to many walking and biking paths,
        restaurants, Autzen Stadium and the University of Oregon campus.
</string>
    <string name="mount_pisgah_name">Mount Pisgah</string>
    <string name="mount_pisgah_address">34901 Frank Parrish Rd\nEugene OR 97405</string>
    <string name="mount_pisgah_phone">541.747.3817</string>
    <string name="mount_pisgah_website">http://www.mountpisgaharboretum.org/</string>
    <string name="mount_pisgah_details">A variety of easy to moderate loop trails from 0.5 miles to
        1.5 miles (0,3 km to 1,2 km) make Mt. Pisgah a great place for all ages and abilities to
        explore. The trails wind along the river through trees and wildflowers labeled to help
        visitors learn plant identification. Watch for bullfrogs and turtles in the water garden.
        Mt. Pisgah Arboretum provides maps of trails throughout the park. Adjacent Howard Buford
        Recreation Area offers longer and more strenuous hikes. DAY-USE FEE AREA/RECREATION PASS
        REQUIRED
</string>
    <string name="spencer_butte_name">Spencer Butte Trail</string>
    <string name="spencer_butte_address">85385 Willamette St\nEugene OR 97405</string>
    <string name="spencer_butte_phone">541.682.4800</string>
    <string name="spencer_butte_website">https://www.eugene-or.gov/Facilities/Facility/Details/
        Ridgeline-Trail-System-129</string>
    <string name="spencer_butte_details">This moderate to difficult 1.7 mile (2,7 km) loop trail
        climbs 784 ft (235 m) before reaching the summit of Spencer Butte. The 360-degree view from
        the summit makes this short but challenging trail worth the effort for hikers of all ages.
        Look for views of the Three Sisters and Fern Ridge Reservoir. Connect this trail with other
        sections of the Ridgeline Trail System for a longer hike. Watch for poison oak and rattle
        snakes along the trail.
</string>
    <string name="pres_trail_name">Pre\'s Trail</string>
    <string name="pres_trail_address">Alton Baker Park and Willamette River\nEugene OR 97401</string>
    <string name="pres_trail_phone">541.682.4800</string>
    <string name="pres_trail_website">https://www.eugene-or.gov/1727/Pres-Trail</string>
    <string name="pres_trail_details">Follow in the footsteps of legendary track star Steve
        Prefontaine on this scenic path located by Alton Baker Park. The path has loops from 1 mile
        to 10,000 meters and is a soft, bark covered trail. You can also connect the trail to the
        Willamette River Trail.
</string>
    <string name="bier_stein_name">The Bier Stein Bottleshop and Pub</string>
    <string name="bier_stein_address">1591 Willamette St\nEugene OR 97401</string>
    <string name="bier_stein_phone">541.485.2437</string>
    <string name="bier_stein_website">http://thebierstein.com/</string>
    <string name="bier_stein_details">Since they opened in 2005, the Bier Stein Bottleshop and
        Taphouse features Eugene\'s largest beer selection. This European-style bottleshop offers
        over 1,000 bottled beers and over 30 on tap. Pair with soups, salads, appetizers, deli
        sandwiches and grilled paninis. Their knowledgeable staff can help you choose from their
        vast selection. Billard table and comfortable seating.
</string>
    <string name="cafe_440_name">Café 440</string>
    <string name="cafe_440_address">440 Coburg Rd\nEugene OR 97401</string>
    <string name="cafe_440_phone">541.505.8493</string>
    <string name="cafe_440_website">http://www.cafe440.com/</string>
    <string name="cafe_440_details">Comfort food with a modern twist is the motto at Café 440, where
        Chef Kathryn Nordgren is creating delicious meals out of locally grown products. Menu items
        such as country fried chicken, shepherd\'s pie and salmon fish and chips won\'t disappoint.
        Serving lunch, dinner and Sunday brunch. Local artists Shelley James and Callan Coleman
        perform every other Tuesday evening with a portion of the sales from those nights going to
        local charities.
</string>
    <string name="beppe_name">Beppe and Gianni\'s Trattoria</string>
    <string name="beppe_address">1646 E 19th Ave\nEugene OR 97403</string>
    <string name="beppe_phone">541.683.6661</string>
    <string name="beppe_website">http://beppeandgiannis.net/</string>
    <string name="beppe_detail">Consistently voted \'Eugene\'s Best Italian Restaurant\' by The
        Register Guard, Beppe and Gianni\'s is a staple in the Eugene community. They offer a sunny,
        warm Tuscan villa ambiance to the University of Oregon campus, with a cuisine to match. They
        offer an incredible authentic menu with an extensive wine list. They've been serving
        traditional Italian cuisine since 1998.
</string>
    <string name="hult_center_name">Hult Center for the Performing Arts</string>
    <string name="hult_center_address">7th Ave and Willamette St\nEugene OR 97401</string>
    <string name="hult_center_phone">541.682.5000</string>
    <string name="hult_center_website">http://www.hultcenter.org/</string>
    <string name="hult_center_details">A regional performing arts center, located in the heart of
        downtown Eugene, next door to the Hilton hotel. The two beautiful theaters, the Silva
        Concert Hall can seat 2,500 and the Soreng Theater can seat 500 people. The Studio provides
        space for receptions, meetings, lectures and presentations. They are the host to world-class
        performances and conference sessions. Resident companies include the Eugene Opera, Eugene
        Symphony, Eugene Concert Choir, Eugene Ballet, Ballet Fantastique and Fred Crafts' Radio
        Redux. Nationally touring headliners, Broadway and dance shows regularly grace the stage.
</string>
    <string name="the_shedd_name">The John G. Shedd Institute for the Arts</string>
    <string name="the_shedd_address">868 High St\nEugene OR 97401</string>
    <string name="the_shedd_phone">541.687.6526</string>
    <string name="the_shedd_website">http://www.theshedd.org/</string>
    <string name="the_shedd_details">The Shedd Institute offers concerts, conferences, lectures,
        classes and other events year-round; including four unique concert series\'. The Shedd
        Community Music School offers classes, private lessons and music education. They also put on
        the Oregon Festival of American Music every August. This historic building and venue is
        located in downtown Eugene.
</string>
    <string name="museum_name">The Museum of Natural and Cultural History</string>
    <string name="museum_address">1680 E 15th Ave\nEugene OR 97403</string>
    <string name="museum_phone">541.346.3024</string>
    <string name="museum_website">http://natural-history.uoregon.edu/</string>
    <string name="museum_description">At this world-class museum, visitors explore 15,000 years of
        Oregon\'s cultural history and 300 million years of its natural history and geology in a
        Northwest Coast longhouse-inspired building. From the world\'s oldest shoes to the giant
        sabertooth salmon, the museum celebrates Oregon\'s deep history through striking imagery,
        rare artifacts and fossils, and hands-on displays for visitors of all ages. General
        admission is $5 with discounts for seniors and youth. Guided exhibit talks are offered daily
        at 2 p.m. Free admission on the first Friday each month.
</string>

</resources>
